zopag.com 2009-10-04

# zopag.com Privacy Policy

Zopag.com is a subsidiary of Growvision Networks Pvt. Ltd. Zopag is located at www.zopag.com. It deals with news, live breaking news, photos, live discussion forums etc. 

Your privacy is important to us. Our privacy policy is simple. To avail certain sites/services on Zopag.com, we ask our readers to provide certain information for the registration process namely:- a) your name, b) email address, c) gender, d) age, e) PIN code etc., and / or your occupation etc. You may read 'About Us' to know more about Zopag at http://www.zopag.com/aboutus.php. 

If you visit our website just to browse, read or download information, but do not register for any of our services, we collect and store certain information about your visit automatically. But these are no personal details. This automatically collected information includes the type of browser you are using (e.g. Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of Operating System you have (e.g. Windows '98 or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet Service Provider (e.g. America Online, Satyam Online, Mantra Online, VSNL), the date and time of your visit, and the pages you visit. This non-personally identifiable information is used to improve our website(s) design, content and primarily to give you a better browsing experience. 

We collect personal information like your name, address, e-mail address and your interests in and use of various services from you, only if you provide it voluntarily. For example, you might submit your name and e-mail address to subscribe to our newsletters or to take part in our discussion forum or to send us your feedback. You might also enter another person's e-mail address and name and yours when you use our 'Mail This Story' feature. The information you provide is not given or sold to any other organisation or person. 

Information from Third-Party Sites and Sponsors Our website sometimes contain links to other websites whose privacy policies may be different from ours. Consult the privacy notes of these sites' before doing so, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. The advertisements that you see on our pages are also served by a reputable third party. In the course of serving these advertisements, our third-party advertiser may place or recognise a unique 'cookie' on your browser and may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Zopag.com servers automatically collect very limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to measure traffic within our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors come from. 

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to editor@zopag.com or by mail addressed to Zopag (Privacy Policy) Growvision Networks Pvt. Ltd., B-1/3, III Floor, Paschim Vihar, New Delhi - 110063
